(Sheldon:)Now that Leonard's made me aware
of how high the genetic stakes are...
(Sheldon:)...we have to face the fact
that none of you are suitable for my sister.
(Howard:)Wait a minute,
Leonard made you aware of that?
(Leonard:)We all make mistakes. Let's move on.
(Raj:)Excuse me, but I think you're missing
a big opportunity here.
- How so?
- Everybody knows genetic diversity...
(Raj:)...produces the strongest offspring.
(Raj:)Why not put a little mocha
in the family latte?
(Sheldon:)In principle, you have a point.
(Sheldon:)But as a practical matter, need I remind you
it takes experimental pharmaceuticals...
(Sheldon:)...to simply enable you
to speak to the opposite sex?
I think you're focusing
entirely too much on the drugs.
Is it because I'm Jewish?
Because I'd kill my rabbi with a pork chop
to be with your sister.